=Let's Go Fighting= =Episode 16=
= لنبدأ القتال = = الحلقة 16 =
You are two peas in a pod.
أنت اثنين من البازلاء في جراب.
No wonder even I didn't recognize you.
لا عجب حتى أنني لم أتعرف عليك.
You know me?
أنت تعرفني؟
Mr. Mu mentioned you before.
ذكرك السيد مو من قبل.
But,
ولكن،
Miss Mu,
ملكة جمال مو ،
these materials
هذه المواد
can only prove that
يمكن فقط إثبات ذلك
you are Mr. Mu's daughter.
أنت ابنة السيد مو.
Under the Articles of Association of the Mu Group,
بموجب النظام الأساسي لمجموعة Mu ،
the appointment of directors
تعيين المديرين
is subject to a vote of the shareholders.
يخضع لتصويت المساهمين.
No wonder Xia Xingrun
لا عجب شيا Xingrun
can expose my identity
يمكن أن يفضح هويتي
so fearlessly.
بلا خوف.
(The Mu Group Will Change the President The MOHS Group Expressed Their Protest)
(ستغير مجموعة Mu الرئيس وأعربت مجموعة وزارة الصحة والخدمات الاجتماعية عن احتجاجها)
Boss, Miss Mu will be sad
سيد ، الآنسة مو سوف تكون حزينة
if you do this.
إذا قمت بذلك.
People don't understand me.
الناس لا يفهمونني.
Don't you understand me?
الا تفهمني
Li,
لي ،
bad news.
اخبار سيئة.
Look,
نظرة،
The MOHS publicly supports Xia Xingrun.
تدعم وزارة الصحة والخدمات العامة Xia Xingrun علنًا.
(The Mos is planning to abandon Mu Liu) Originally, I wanted to get more votes
(يخطط The Mos للتخلي عن Mu Liu) في الأصل ، كنت أرغب في الحصول على المزيد من الأصوات
with Mo Chen's support
(يخطط The Mos للتخلي عن Mu Liu) بدعم من Mo Chen
(The Mos is planning to abandon Mu Liu) at the general meeting of shareholders.
(يخطط Mos للتخلي عن Mu Liu) في الاجتماع العام للمساهمين.
(The Mu Group Will Change the President The MOHS Group Expressed Their Protest)
(ستغير مجموعة Mu الرئيس وأعربت مجموعة وزارة الصحة والخدمات الاجتماعية عن احتجاجها)
That's really a piece of good news.
هذا حقًا خبر سار.
Mr. Xia,
السيد شيا ،
I'm very interested in the Italian ENI Dessert project.
أنا مهتم جدًا بمشروع ENI Dessert الإيطالي.
(MOHS Group) (OK.)
(مجموعة MOHS) (موافق.)
(I will also send you the information about ENI Dessert.)
(سأرسل لك أيضًا معلومات حول ENI Dessert.)
(Related data and account information of ENI Dessert)
(البيانات ذات الصلة ومعلومات الحساب الخاصة بـ ENI Dessert)
Boss,
رئيس،
look at this.
انظر الى هذا.
(Cooperation Agreement; ENI Dessert and Starwu Investment)
(اتفاقية تعاون ؛ ENI Dessert و Starwu Investment)
(Account Number: Xia Xingrun)
(رقم الحساب: Xia Xingrun)
(Xia Xingrun: You've got ENI's data and account. What about my money?)
(Xia Xingrun: لديك بيانات وحساب ENI. ماذا عن أموالي؟)
(Mo Chen: It'll be paid to you soon. Mr. Xia, please wait.)
(مو تشين: سيتم الدفع لك قريبًا. السيد شيا ، من فضلك انتظر.)
Everybody's here.
الجميع هنا.
Just waiting for you.
فقط بانتظارك.
By the way,
على فكرة،
what
ماذا او ما
should I call you?
هل علي ان اتصل بك؟
Mu Li.
مو لي.
Mr. Luo
السيد لو
has told me
قال لي
about Miss Mu.
حول الآنسة مو.
There's no problem with her identity.
لا توجد مشكلة في هويتها.
Even if Miss Mu's identity is OK,
حتى لو كانت هوية الآنسة مو على ما يرام ،
it's a fact
انها حقيقة
that she colluded with outsiders
أنها تواطأت مع الغرباء
to transfer the Mu Group's property.
لنقل ملكية مجموعة Mu.
Speaking of transfer property,
بالحديث عن نقل الملكية ،
I also have a document here
لدي أيضا وثيقة هنا
for Mr. Xia to read.
للسيد شيا للقراءة.
This is the business file
هذا هو ملف العمل
of the ENI Dessert Project,
مشروع ENI للحلويات ،
lost by Mr. Lu.
خسرها السيد لو.
(Bank Account Transaction Details; Xia Xingrun)
(تفاصيل معاملات الحساب المصرفي ؛ Xia Xingrun)
(Total income amount) Mr. Xia,
(إجمالي مبلغ الدخل) السيد شيا ،
how do you explain
كيف تشرح
this record of capital transactions
هذا السجل للمعاملات الرأسمالية
with ENI Dessert?
مع حلوى ENI؟
You faked these.
أنت زيفت هذه.
(Invitation for Invitation to Study Tour Introduction to ENI Dessert Mu Group)
(دعوة لدعوة جولة دراسية مقدمة لمجموعة ENI Dessert Mu Group)
My father went to Italy
ذهب والدي إلى إيطاليا
to study the ENI Dessert project,
لدراسة مشروع ENI Dessert ،
which was planned by you, Mr. Xia?
الذي خططت له يا سيد شيا؟
You must have something to do with My father's accident.
يجب أن يكون لديك شيء لتفعله مع حادث والدي.
Mu Li!
مو لي!
You're slinging mud at me!
أنت ترفع الطين في وجهي!
Then I will give you one day
ثم سأعطيك يوما ما
to prove yourself.
لتثبت نفسك.
But Mr. Xia,
لكن السيد شيا ،
don't run away.
لا تهرب.
Li,
لي ،
how did you find these records?
كيف وجدت هذه السجلات؟
It was Mo Chen's idea.
كانت فكرة مو تشن.
When you left that day.
عندما غادرت ذلك اليوم.
Do you believe me?
هل تصدقني؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Of course, I believe you.
بالطبع أنا أصدقك.
Tell me the situation now,
قل لي الوضع الآن ،
and listen to me.
واستمع لي.
That's the way it is.
هكذا هي.
Mr. D,
السيد.  د،
hurry up and arrange my ticket to Italy!
عجلوا ورتبوا تذكرتي إلى إيطاليا!
(Why are you in such a hurry?)
(لماذا أنت في عجلة من أمرك؟)
(Did they find out about the accident?)
(هل علموا بالحادث؟)
Yes!
نعم!
I arranged the itinerary for the day.
لقد رتبت خط سير الرحلة لهذا اليوم.
It was just an accident.
كان مجرد حادث.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
But I was at the scene
لكنني كنت في مكان الحادث
of the accident.
من الحادث.
Are you going to
هل أنت ذاهب إلى
leave me in the lurch?
اتركني في الترنح؟
It's not that I leave me in the lurch,
ليس الأمر أنني أتركني في الترنح ،
but that you deserved it.
لكنك تستحقها.
You...
أنت...
How did you do it?
كيف فعلتها؟
Mr. Xia is very cautious.
السيد شيا حذر جدا.
We have an important thing to discuss,
لدينا شيء مهم نناقشه ،
so, we'd better be careful.
لذلك ، من الأفضل أن نكون حذرين.
Mo Chen,
مو تشين ،
thank you very much.
شكرا جزيلا لك.
Are there any rewards?
هل هناك مكافآت؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I want...
أريد...
(Li.)
(لي.)
Ah.
آه.
You
أنت
think about it and take your time.
فكر في الأمر وخذ وقتك.
I'll go out first.
سأخرج أولا.
Eh.
إيه.
Mu Li,
مو لي ،
you are no match for Mr. D.
أنت لا تتطابق مع السيد د.
You'd better think about yourself first.
من الأفضل أن تفكر في نفسك أولاً.
For your father's sake,
من أجل والدك
I'll give you a hint.
سأعطيك تلميحا.
Whether you can get it
ما إذا كان يمكنك الحصول عليها
depends on your ability.
يعتمد على قدرتك.
(Hello?)
(مرحبًا؟)
Mr. D,
السيد.  د،
who are you?
من أنت؟
(We'll meet soon.)
(سنلتقي قريبا.)
It's just the beginning of the game.
إنها مجرد بداية اللعبة.
(Mr. Mo,)
(السيد مو)
don't admit defeat first.
لا تعترف بالهزيمة أولاً.
Mu Bingyun
مو بينجيون
and Xia Xingrun,
وشيا Xingrun ،
you are all rubbish!
كلكم هراء!
Finally,
أخيراً،
I have to do it myself.
علي أن أفعل ذلك بنفسي.
(Chen,)
(تشين)
(I will take everything)
(سآخذ كل شيء)
you want
انت تريد
little by little.
شيأ فشيأ.
=Let's Go Fighting=
= لنبدأ القتال =
♪The soul falls to the bottom of the lake♪
الروح تسقط في قاع البحيرة
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪ النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪